http://www.suebox.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This web site is owned and operated by Sue Box Creations Pty Ltd ABN 70 095 783 412 and will be referred to as "We", "our" and "us" in this Internet Privacy Policy. By using this site, you agree to the Internet Privacy Policy of this web site ("the web site"), which is set out on this web site page. The Internet Privacy Policy relates to the collection and use of personal information you may supply to us through your conduct on the web site.
We reserve the right, at our discretion, to modify or remove portions of this Internet Privacy Policy at any time. This Internet Privacy Policy is in addition to any other terms and conditions applicable to the web site. We do not make any representations about third party web sites that may be linked to the web site. This Internet Privacy Policy is also separate from the Privacy Policy of Sue Box Creations Pty Ltd, which is available upon reasonable request.
We recognise the importance of protecting the privacy of information collected about visitors to our web site, in particular information that is capable of identifying an individual ("personal information"). This Internet Privacy Policy governs the manner in which your personal information, obtained through the web site, will be dealt with. This Internet Privacy Policy should be reviewed periodically so that you are updated on any changes. We welcome your comments and feedback.
Personal Information
Personal information about visitors to our site is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted. For example, we may need to collect such information to provide you with further services or to answer or forward any requests or enquiries. It is our intention that this policy will protect your personal information from being dealt with in any way that is inconsistent with applicable privacy laws in Australia.
Use of Information
Personal information that visitors submit to our site is used only for the purpose for which it is submitted or for such other secondary purposes that are related to the primary purpose, unless we disclose other uses in this Internet Privacy Policy or at the time of collection. Copies of correspondence sent from the web site, that may contain personal information, are stored as archives for record-keeping and back-up purposes only. You should be aware that providing information through our site will result in the information being passed to our staff and your information will then be held subject to the privacy obligations of our staff which may not conform with this Internet Privacy Policy.
Disclosure
Apart from where you have consented or disclosure is necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was submitted, personal information may be disclosed in special situations where we have reason to believe that doing so is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against anyone damaging, injuring, or interfering (intentionally or unintentionally) with our rights or property, users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. Also, we may disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires disclosure.
We may engage third parties to provide you with goods or services on our behalf. In that circumstance, we may disclose your personal information to those third parties in order to meet your request for goods or services.
Security
We strive to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personal information submitted to our sites, and we review and update our security measures in light of current technologies. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure.
However, we will endeavor to take all reasonable steps to protect the personal information you may transmit to us or from our online products and services. No credit card information is captured or stored on our website. All Credit card payments are processed by trusted internet payment providers such as PayPal and Googlepay.
In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services related to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by us. However, we will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorized access to your personal information.
Access to Information
We will endeavor to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you, and to keep this information accurate and up to date. If, at any time, you discover that information held about you is incorrect, you may contact us to have the information corrected.
In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services related to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by us.
Problems or questions
If we become aware of any ongoing concerns or problems with our web sites, we will take these issues seriously and work to address these concerns. If you have any further queries relating to our Privacy Policy, or you have a problem or complaint, please email peter@suebox.com
Further Privacy Information
For more information about privacy issues in Australia and protecting your privacy, visit the Australian Federal Privacy Commissioner's web site.
Personally Identifiable Information
Sue Box Creations Pty Ltd will not collect any personally identifiable information about you (that is, your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) unless you provide it to us voluntarily. If you do not want your personally identifiable information collected, please do not submit it to us. If you have already submitted this information and would like for us to remove it from our records, please contact us at the Site. We will use reasonable efforts to delete your information from our existing files. When you do provide us with personally identifiable information, we may use that information in the following ways, unless stated otherwise: we may store and process that information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services; we may use that information to contact you; to protect our rights or property.
Children
Sue Box Creations Pty Ltd has no intention of collecting any personally identifiable information (that is, name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) from individuals under eighteen (18) years of age. Where appropriate, Sue Box Creations Pty Ltd will specifically instruct children not to submit such information on our Site. If a child has provided us with personally identifiable information, a parent or guardian of that child should contact us at the e-mail address or phone number listed on our website if they would like this information deleted from our records. We will use reasonable efforts to delete the child's information from our existing files.
Non Personally Identifiable Information Collected Automatically
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet Browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the domain name of the Site from which you linked to our Site or advertisement.
Cookies
When you view one of our Sites or advertisements, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "Cookie" or similar file and will help us in many ways. For example, Cookies allow us to tailor a Site or advertisement to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.
Who to Contact
If you have submitted personally identifiable information through this Site or interactive advertisement, and would like that information deleted from our records, please send an e-mail with your details and a contact number to our consumer relations department using our email address peter@suebox.com We will use reasonable efforts to delete this information from our existing files. Further questions? Contact us via our email peter@suebox.com or call us on +61 7 3879 6464 in Australia.
Basis of Privacy Policy Principles
The privacy principles of this Policy are based on respect for international standards of privacy protection, such as the Information Privacy Principles set out in section 14 of the Commonwealth Privacy Act, 1998 and the Australian Privacy Charter.
choosing a selection results in a full page refresh
